--=制作：糖涂口=--
女主人  打我屁股  用力打
Mistress, spank my bottom. Spank it really hard!
请打我屁股
Please, spank my bottom!
-真恶心  -用力打
- That is unpleasant. -Spank it really hard.
舔我乳头
Lick my nipples.
不了  谢谢  胖女人
No, thank you, pregnant lady.
脱衣 士兵们
Strip, soldier!
你们就会知道为什么他们叫我操练军官
You're gonna find out why they call me the drill sergeant.
真爽  宝贝
That's... that's nice, baby.
不要  卷毛  不要
No, Frizzy! no!
不要  不要 不要 卷毛  不要弄
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
卷毛
Frizzy.
不要 不要 等等 科迪 不要
No, no, no, wait! Cody! No.
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
别担心  伙计  谁都有性爱录像
Don't worry about it, man. Everyone's got a sex tape.
算了吧
Please.
是阿  只是他们是跟人在做爱
Yeah, except they're having sex with people.
-卷毛  -对
-Frizzy. - Right.
如果你的家庭是特殊物种的话
It's not technically incest
理论上不算是乱伦
If your family member's a different species.
所以  你跟达娜有什么进展吗
So, are you getting close with Dana yet?
谣言是真的  她发誓禁欲
The rumours are true. She's taken the pledge.
禁欲  你对她可是很有把握的啊
No sex? She was your sure thing.
-信念夏令营的宣传  伙计  她等结婚后再做爱
-Faith-camp propaganda, man. She's waiting until marriage.
我以为她和六个男生做过爱
I thought she had sex with six guys.
怎么了
What?
进教室去
Get to class.
走廊上不准用手机  艾莉森
No cell phones in the hall, Alyson.
放学之后去我办公室拿
You can pick this up from my office today after school.
不要  不要 不要  卷毛  不要 卷毛
No, no, no,Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
我还看过更糟糕的
Well, I've seen worse.
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
约翰逊小姐 一起吃午饭吗
Miss Johnson. Lunch today?
我得先看看日程表  变态...皮特
I'll have to check my calendar, perv...Pete.
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要  卷毛
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
看  看  看这个
Look. Look. Look at that.
不要 不要 不要 卷毛  不要 卷毛
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
-嘿  别管他们  -噢  天啊 你也看到了
- Hey, just ignore them. -Oh, god. You saw it, too?
你知道 那不是
Just so you know, it's not at all...
不要紧
Hey, don't worry about it.
卷毛是只很好看的狗
Frizzy's a good-looking dog.
所以  你想做吗  我们上吗
So, do you wanna do it? Are we on?
罗伯  罗伯  我们上不上第七节课吗
Rob? Rob? Are we on for seventh period?
好  我
Yeah. l...i'll...
- 我等会去找你  -好
- I'll meet you over there. -Okay.
-狗交狂  -嘿  斯戴福尔
- Doggy style! - Hey, stifler.
那是你女朋友吗
Is that your girlfriend?
不是  我们  我们只是  我们只是朋友
No, we're just...we're just...we're friends.
只是朋友  真好
Just friends? How sweet.
她看上去真成熟
Well, she seems awful ripe.
如果你不偷禁果  那我就偷了
If you don't pick the fruit, I will.
嘿  美女
Hey, beautiful.
早上好  东大瀑布高中的开拓者
Good morning, east great falls blazers.
别忘了本周对抗中央高中的比赛
Don't forget about the big game against central this week
欢迎舞会从晚上七点举办到午夜
And the aloha dance this friday from 7:00 to midnight.
建议入场的时候穿戴夏威夷衫和花环
Hawaiian shirts and leis are recommended for entrance.
-查尔斯  关掉那个  -不好意思
- Charles, knock that off. -Sorry.
请专心考试
Let's focus on the quiz, please.
混蛋
Douche bag.
你知道  我是认真发誓的
I'm serious about this pledge, you know.
我知道
I know.
-所以今晚我只跳舞  -行  只跳舞
- So just dancing tonight. - Yeah. Just dancing.
横向呼啦舞
The horizontal hula.
内森
Nathan.
可怜的内森
Poor Nathan.
他的小弟弟肯定硬得能够割草了
His willy must be hard enough to cut glass by now.
内森爱我  也很尊重我
Nathan loves me, and nathan respects me.
一  男人永远不会尊重一个不要性爱的女人
Okay. A, a guy never respects a girl enough to give up sex.
二  那你呢
And, B, well, what about you?
你现在肯定觉得性欲特强吧 达娜
You must be feeling pretty randy by now, Dana.
好吧  可能有那么一点点吧
Okay, well, yeah, maybe, like, the tiniest bit,
但我真觉得自己有极强的控制力
But I really feel like I'm connecting with the higher power here.
是  我知道  这非常好啊
Yes, I know, and that is totally fab,
我就不行了  我太热衷于口交了
But I know I couldn't do it. I'm way too into giving blow jobs.
问问理查德就知道了
Ask Richard.
别听伊莫金的好吗
Hey, don't listen to Lmogen, okay?
性爱还是很重要的  如果你觉得还没准备好
Sex is a really big deal, and if you feel like you're not ready,
那我认为你应该再等等
Then I think you should wait.
但是
But...
无意冒犯  海蒂  你根本不知道自己在说什么
No offence,Heidi, but you have no idea what you're talking about.
等下给我发短信
Text me later.
-嘿  罗伯  -怎么了
-Hey, Rob. -Yeah?
-我可以问你一些事吗  -当然  什么事
-Can I ask you something? - Sure. What's up?
个人的一些事情
Well, it's kind of personal.
没问题
Okay.
我一直在想  你知道我还是处女吧
I've been thinking. You know I'm a virgin, right?
只是  我不知道
It's just...I don't know.
好像别人已经做过一百万次爱了
Everyone's already done it like a million times already,
我知道我还没有男朋友  但是
And I know I don't have a boyfriend or whatever, but...
有时候我感觉我应该去试试
But sometimes I feel like I should just get it over with.
你知道吗   我是说我想破处
You know? I mean, just get past this whole thing, this virgin.
那到底是什么意思呢
What does that even mean, anyway?
还没有小弟弟插进过我阴道  但是那又怎样
So I've never had a penis in my vagina, but so what?
为什么我要记得这些事  比如  她太单纯了
Why do I have to label everything? like, "She's too innocent."
肯定不能做爱
She can't handle it.
我一点都不单纯
I'm not that innocent.
我看过《脱衣舞娘》和《蓝色珊瑚》
I've seen Showgirls and Blue Lagoon.
总之  我决定去试试  你觉得怎么样
Anyways, I think I've decided to just do it. But what do you think?
是啊  我觉得你应该把这事给做圆满了
Yeah. I think you should definitely go ahead and get it over with.
谢了
Thanks.
回到学习上去吧
Let's get back to work.
斯戴福尔正在欢迎舞会上为你做现场直播
Stifler  coming at you live from the aloha dance
这里是东大瀑布
Here at the east great falls...
这个妞刚刚抓了我屁股
This chick just grabbed my ass.
她想玩玩斯戴福尔的小弟弟
She wants to play the stifmeister's flute skin.
一起去找找那些长相甜美的美女吧  吉普西
Let go find some of that sweet-looking pinoche, Gibbsy.
看那边  海蒂在那里
Hey, check it out. There's Heidi.
不错  不错  她看上去容易得手
All right, all right. She looks highly doable.
所以游戏计划是什么
All right, so what's the game plan here?
我不知道  我想应该请她跳舞
I don't know. Ask her to dance, I guess.
你得有个计划  知道吗
You need a plan, all right?
这样你才能建立目标
It's all about establishing your intentions.
看  现在  她只觉得你是个朋友
See, right now, she thinks of you as just a friend.
你需要打破这个形象
You need to break that paradigm.
记住  朋友不会让朋友只是朋友
Remember, friends don't let friends just be friends.
-没错  -我说真的  你别搞黄了
-Right. - I'm serious. you cannot puss out here.
知道了 别紧张   我会去跟她说的
All right, take it easy. I'm gonna go talk to her.
等等  难道你没忘记什么吗
Wait. Aren't you forgetting something?
这里  可别忘了这个
Here, don't forget these.
这是你孤单的时候需要的东西
You only need those when you're alone.
对  对  好吧
Right. Right. Okay.
-好了  -什么  怎么了
-Okay! -What? What's wrong?
我不能
I can't.
-才到二垒  -我知道  但是如果我们进行到那里
-But it's only second base. -I know. But if we go there,
我们会更深入进去的
Then we're gonna wanna go further.
可亚当和夏娃都做爱了
But Adam and Eve did it.
对不起  嘿
I'm sorry. Hey, hey.
我爱你  你知道吗
I love you. Do you know that?
来吧
Come here.
那上帝接受口交吗
Is god okay with a blow job?
我以为你知道我有多在乎这件事
I thought you understood how I felt about this.
我告诉你  结婚前
I told you, it's important for me
保持贞操对我来说很重要
To save myself until marriage.
你都跟七个男生做过了
You've had sex with seven guys.
是六个  不是七个
And it was six, not seven!
其中一人是黑人  他一人顶两人
Well, one was a black guy, so he counts as two.
达娜
Dana.
-达娜  别生气  -滚开
-Dana, come on. -Fuck off.
达娜  过来吧  达娜  达娜
Dana. Come on, Dana. Dana!
嘿  小妞们  这个会放到我的脸书网上面
Hey, girls. This is gonna be for sit-on-my-face-book.
你们亲一下好吗
I need you to kiss one time, okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
来吧  数百万人会点击看的
Come on. It's gonna be seen by millions of people.
好吧
Okay.
好了 我们再来一次
Okay, we're gonna go again,
但是这一次   给爸爸伸出舌头
But this time, sneak in some tongue for daddy.
好吧
Okay.
我说的就是这样  宝贝
That's what I'm talking about, baby!
斯戴福尔再次袭来
Stifmeister strikes again!
伙计
Dude.
你肯定会喜欢这个  看看吧
You're gonna love this. Check this out.
是啊  所以呢
Yeah. So?
看着跟我学学
Watch and learn.
你真性感
"You're hot."
给我你的电话号码
"Give me your number "
一起出去玩吧
"And let's get together"
我把这个丢给一位辣妹
I throw this at a hot girl,
然后她很有兴趣
And she's so impressed that
我的阴谋就得逞了
I'm literally throwing around a benjamin
接着她会想认识认识我
That she wants to hook up with me.
好吧  祝你好运
Yeah. Good luck with that.
-我要去找达娜  -好吧
-I'm gonna go find dana. -All right, man.
糟了
Oh, no.
天啊
Oh, god.
借过  借过  小心  有人要过去
Excuse me, excuse me, Watch out. Coming through.
我在想之前说的那些话
So, I was thinking about what
你知道之前那些
We were talking about, you know, before.
-是的  是的  我记得  -好  所以我想还等什么呢
-Yeah. Yeah, I remember. -Right. So I was thinking, why wait?
对吗   我是说你也想了却这么一桩事
Right? I mean, you might as well, you know, get it over with.
什么  在这里  舞会上吗
What? Like, here? At the dance?
通常都是在图书馆
Well, there's always the library.
-对  图书馆     -我开玩笑的
-Yeah, the library. - I'm kidding.
-我知道  -但是说真的  舞会完了之后
-Yeah. I know. -But seriously, after the dance,
我不知道是否你
I don't know if you...
-你在干什么  -找我的钱
-What are you doing? -Looking for my money.
-那一百块吗  -是的
-C-note thing? -Yeah.
-钱没了吗  -闭嘴
-Lose your money? -Shut up.
回神啦  怎么了  伙计  海蒂在哪
And we're back. What's up, dude? Where's Heidi?
我不知道
I don't know.
她几秒前还在这  可能上厕所去了
She was here a second ago. Maybe she went to the bathroom.
-是啊  可能     -达娜现在很生我气
-Yeah, maybe. -Dana's pissed at me.
伙计   你得陪着她守住誓言
Dude, you gotta play along with this whole pledge thing.
对你来说是简单
Well, that's easy for you to say.
你也没有真正搞到她啊
You haven't exactly broken the seal yet, either.
伙计  我平时都能打到三垒
Dude, I've been getting to third base on a regular basis.
而且我现在都不打飞机了
I can't go back to jacking off now.
伙计  你用左手打飞机会有很不一样的感觉
Dude, just use your left hand. It feels completely different.
-我要去找海蒂   -我也去找达娜
-I'm gonna go find Heidi. -I'm gonna go find Dana.
小子 你差点把我推倒
No! dude, you're gonna make me hurl.
海蒂
Heidi?
不要  不要  不要
No, no, no, no!
等等
Wait.
兄弟  嘿
Dude, yo.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
罗伯  你说
Rob? you said...
罗伯
Rob!
兄弟  来的真是时候
Dude, nice cock block.
我着火了
I'm on fire.
-我着火了  -天啊
- I'm on fire. -Oh, my god.
着火了  着火了  我身上着火了
There's a fire. there's a fire, and it's on me.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
罗伯  罗伯  把它扑灭  把你裤子脱了
Rob! Rob! put it out. Take off your pants!
快脱了  把你裤子脱了
Take off...Take your pants off!
天啊
Oh, god!
快点
Come on!
我的天啊  我的天啊  我的天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
快点  罗伯  快
Hurry, Rob, Come on.
把火熄灭   把火熄灭
Get it out! Get it out!
天啊
Oh, god.
该死的  发生什么事了
What the hell is going on in here?
为期两个月的每周六
Two months seems like an awfully
留堂也太长了吧
Long time for saturday detention.
我们应该是去打扫图书馆
We're supposed to clean up the library.
你们知道吸尘器在哪吗
Do you guys know where the vacuum is?
不知道
Nope.
你当时到底在图书馆做什么
What were you doing in the library anyway?
什么都没做  当时海蒂已经在那了
I wasn't doing anything. Heidi was already in there.
-我只是去找她  -我听说她在帮某男口交
-I was just looking for her. -I heard she was blowing some dude.
科迪  如果你被留堂的话
Cody! well, I don't know how you're
我不知道
Gonna go on the school ski trip
你还怎么参加学校的滑雪旅行
If you're still on detention.
妈  我不懂两者有什么关系  我什么都没做
Mom, I don't see what that has to do with it. I didn't do anything.
我听说你就是那个男的
I heard you were the fluffer.
-科迪  -看  他的嘴唇都裂开了
-Cody. -Look. Lis lips are chapped.
再看吧
Well, we'll see.
好了  我要去准备一下了
All right. I have to go get ready.
可能吸尘器在仓库
Maybe it's in the garage.
罗伯  我想跟你谈谈
Rob? I wanna have a little chat with you.
我们有什么好谈的吗
Do we have to?
亲爱的  我知道你长大了
Honey, I know that you're growing older,
我不知道你爸爸跟你说过什么
And I don't know what your father has told you about things,
但是我觉得什么事都应该讨论讨论
But I think it's important to discuss everything, you know?
比如说性
Like about sex.
-你做过爱了吗  -妈  我不想讨论这个事
-Are you having sex? -Mom, I don't wanna talk about this.
不是  我只是在洗衣的时候找到条袜子  而且
No, well, it's just that I found this sock in the laundry, and, well...
天啊  妈  把它扔了
Oh, god, mom. Put that away.
还有  有人给我发了个视频的链接
And, also, somebody sent me a link to this video.
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要
No, no, no, Frizzy! No.
-妈  把那东西关了  -我不知道怎么关
-Mom, just turn it off! -I don't know how!
你弟弟帮我打开的
Your brother made it my start-up screen.
-好了  我能  我能弄好  -你能  太好了
-Okay, I can...I can fix that. You can? Great.
-好  -谢谢
-Yeah. -Thanks.
-不要  不要  卷毛  不要  -谢谢你了
-No, no, no, Frizzy! no! -Thank you for that.
-好吧  -所以我们讨论完了  对吗
-Okay. -And we're done. right? Yeah.
亲爱的  这没什么好羞愧的
Well, honey, please. There's no reason to be ashamed.
手淫是很正常的事
Masturbation is perfectly natural.
你这个年纪的男孩都会想试验一下
I mean, boys your age are maybe into experimentation
跟动物尝试些新东西
And trying new things with animals.
卷毛  我是说她还是小狗的时候
I mean, Frizzy, she's been in our family for...
就来我们家了
Since she was a puppy...
我要迟到了
Hey, I'm late.
-你来迟了  -不好意思
-You're tardy. -Sorry.
你先从清理那些烧过的书开始
You can start by cleaning off all the damaged books
然后把坏的分类出来  我会随时检查
And separating the ruined ones. I'll be checking on you.
Heidi 听着 关于昨天晚上
Heidi. Look, about last night...
我不想谈那个
I don't wanna talk about it.
-我只是想告诉你  -罗伯
-Well, I just wanted to tell you... - Rob.
我去倒脏水
I'm gonna go empty this bucket.
看我找到了什么
Do you have any idea what I found here?
这可是《索爱天书》
This is the Bible.
我以为这只是个都市传说
I thought that was an urban legend.
不  这是真的  这可以追溯到几十年前
No. This is real. This goes back decades.
那又怎样
Okay. So what?
这书可以帮我们把到妹
This is exactly what we need to finally get laid.
这东西怎么帮我们呢  它全毁了
How is this thing gonna help us get laid? It's ruined.
大部分都看不了
You can't even read most of it.
这书每年都帮了
This book has helped one lucky guy
学校里的一位幸运儿
Each year at Great Falls.
今年我们就是幸运儿了
And this year, that lucky guy is us.
虽然这书残缺不全
Even with the damage,
可还是有很多有用的内容
It still has a ton of useful stuff.
看这儿
Check this out.
"1977年2月1日  G点"
"February 1st, 1977. The G-spot:"
-这个我也懂  -还有什么
- I can dig it. - What else you got?
"1991年  如何刮阴毛
"1991. How to shave your pubes
使小弟弟看起来更大"
to make your dick look bigger"
我爸指导过我这个
Dad showed me that one.
"2003年  我经历了最棒的性体验"
"2003. I just had the most amazing sexual experience"
一些看不清了  "她用了薄荷糖"
Something I can't read. "She used a breath mint"
薄荷糖  干嘛的
A breath mint? For what?
你傻啊 在勃起以后
You moron. You stick it up your tailpipe and
薄荷糖能让你的菊花更紧
The minty-ness makes your asshole twitch.
大家都知道啊
Everyone knows that.
我可不知道  听起来不怎么样
Dude, I don't know. This sounds pretty weak.
话说  我觉得
Plus, I mean,
这些大部分都能在网上找到
We can find most of this stuff on the internet anyway.
可不一样  这些都是个人经验之谈
No, this is different. This has personal experiences.
而且  这是为大瀑布高中女孩而写的
Plus, it's custom-tailored to Great Falls girls.
什么时候普纳尼镇有邮编了啊
Since when does Punani have a zip code?
我们有啥损失呢
What have we got to lose?
内森  你和达娜在一起多久了
Nathan, you've been working on Dana for, what?
六个月了吗
Like six months?
才发现她喜欢上帝比喜欢性更多吗
Only to find out that she loves the lord more than sex?
卢贝  你这学期计划中的
And, lube, how have all your schemes
把妹进展如何了
To get laid been working out so far?
损失了100美元
Minus $100.
没错  还有我
Exactly, and me, well,
我一直都在
I've been wasting all my time
浪费时间幻想
On some fantasy that someday
哪天海蒂会爱得我不能自拔
Heidi's gonna fall madly in love with me.
醒醒吧  兄弟们  我们需要帮助
Face it, guys, we need help.
而机会就摆在我们的面前
And this is it, staring us right in the face.
-我加入  -很好
- I'm in. - All right.
我也加入
I'm in.
-耶  -太好了
- Yeah. - Yes.
-耶  -耶
- Yeah! - Yeah!
别激动  兄弟们  这书很旧了
Hey, easy. Guys, it's old.
"1990年5月1日
"May 1st, 1990.
"把到妹最简单的方法就是讨好她"
"The simplest way into a girl's pants is still basic flattery"
就这样吗  讨好她吗
That's it? Just flatter her?
-就是这样  -想想看
- That’s it. - Well, think about it.
你真这么做过几次了
How many times do you actually do it?
走到一个女生面前  然后说  "你眼睛真好看"
Walk up to a girl and say, "Wow, you have beautiful eyes"
好像从来没有
Like, never.
这告诉我们把妹最有效的方法
It's telling us the only proven way
就是要猥琐
To get women is to be an asshole,
因为只有那样的男生
'Cause the guys that actually
才能把到妹
Spew that kind of crap get laid.
快看  12点方向
Check it out. Twelve o'clock.
-好吧  让我们试验下这本书  -好
- All right. Let's put this bible to a test. - Yes.
-你去和她说  -我才不要找艾什莉试
- You go talk to her. - I'm not trying it out on Ashley.
为什么你不去
Why don't you go talk to her,
你不是喜欢她吗
'cause you're the one who likes her?
-我还在吃呢  -好吧  我去
- I'm eating. - Okay. I'll do it.
嗨  艾什莉
Hey, Ashley.
嗨  罗伯  给你女友买东西呢
Hey, Rob. Shopping for your girlfriend?
不  这个  是给我妈的
No...This is...It's for my mom.
她又开始约会了
She's dating again.
呃  其实  我想说
Well, you know, I... Actually, I wanted to say,
那个  你牙齿长得很美
You know, you have the most gorgeous teeth.
跟我来
Hey. Come with me.
嫉妒了吧  他跟你的梦中情人走了
Jealous? He's making a move on your lady friend.
才不像你  我不介意分享我的女人
Unlike you, I don't mind sharing my women.
猥琐男  你们今天要干嘛呢
And what are you wankers up to today?
-你好啊  -嗨  亲爱的
- Cheerio. - Hello, love.
代我向你妈问好
Word to your mumsie.
事实上  我们在等某些女士加入呢
Just waiting for some ladies to join us, in fact.
你们这些娘娘腔
You nancy boys couldn't get laid
别想凭着后台通行证
At a Jonas brothers concert
就在乔纳森兄弟的音乐会上搞到女人
With a fistful of backstage passes.
拜拜了
Cheerio.
她在鄙视我们吗
Was that a slam?
别自己损自己了
You bet your bollocks.
-拿着  -哦
- Hold this. - Yeah.
这个怎么样
How does this look?
很好  我买了
Great, I’ll take it.
站起来
Stand up.
等等  什么...  那个...  别别
Wait, what...what's...Wait, hold...hold on.
我是要打电话给你吗
Should I call you?
走出商店然后去美食区找我就好
Just walk out of the store and meet me at the food court.
自然点
Act natural.
需要什么帮助吗?
Can I help you?
不用  不用  我只是随便看看
No. No. I'm...I’m just browsing.
好吧
Okay, then.
-祝您愉快  -你也是
- Have a nice day. - You, too.
抱歉  我什么都没偷  这只是个恶作剧
I'm sorry! I wasn't stealing. It was a...it was a prank.
抱歉  我想我们忘了给你的商品消磁了
I am so sorry. I think we left the tags on your garments.
麻烦到收银台来  我们会帮您解决的
Please come back to the register. We'll figure this out.
实在抱歉
I'm so embarrassed.
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
对不起...  我有点兴奋了
Sorry, l...i got excited.
149.90美元
That'll be 149.90.
-多少  -149.9美元
- How much? - 149.90.
就这么小的东西
But they're so small.
-你是马德琳  -是我妈  我有她的字条
- Madeleine? - It’s my mom. I'm...i have a note.
-谢谢  -祝您愉快
- Thank you. - Have a nice day.
欢迎下次再来
Come again.
怎么这么久  搞定了吗
What took you so long? Did you get it?
当然 我还帮你偷了个袋子
Sure did. I even stole you a bag
你回家之前都不用碰到它
So you don't have to touch it till you get home.
很好  谢了
Great. Thanks.
嘿  你好啊  艾什莉
Hey. What's up, Ashley?
你们几个同性恋在这个干嘛
What are you pillow biters doing here?
斯蒂夫勒
Stifler.
别吃那个  会增肥的
Don't eat that. You're gonna get fat.
我超级饥渴  想去夏普专卖店搞我吗
I'm super horny. Wanna suck me off in the Sharper Image?
好啊
Okay.
达娜  打扰了  真抱歉
Dana. Excuse me. I'm so sorry.
我不是故意要扰乱...  晨间弥撒的
Didn't mean to disrupt the... This morning's mass.
你来做什么
What are you doing here?
我是来道歉的
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
你觉得现在适合
Did you really think
说这个吗
That this is the best time to discuss this?
可是你都不回我短信
Well, you weren't answering any of my texts.
-我出去一下  行吗  -去吧
- I’ll be right back, okay? -  Okay.
什么是信念
What is faith?
当你按下厨房灯的开关
When you flip the light switch in your kitchen,
你知道灯会亮
You know that the light will turn on.
有人说这就是信念
Some might call that faith,
但我说  这不是真正的信念
but I tell you, that is not the real faith.
好吧 什么事这么重要
Okay, so what is so important
非得你打断弥撒
That you needed to come and interrupt church?
真不明白你现在干嘛这么生我的气
I don't really get why you're so mad at me right now.
因为你不尊重我
Because you don't respect me.
对你来说只是个大笑话
This is all just a big joke to you.
知道吗  你说得没错
You know what? You're right,
这就是你的另一面
Because this is just another face for you.
就像你在做年鉴的时候一样
Just like your little stint on yearbook.
一开始坚持  然后呢
You stuck with that for, what,
两周以后就厌倦了
Two weeks before you got bored with it?
为什么让你相信我希望等到结婚后
Why is it so hard for you to believe that I wanna
再做这件事这么难
Wait until marriage?
因为你一个晚上同时和道格・威尔勒
Because you slept with Doug Wheeler.
还有斯科特・汤普逊睡过
And Scott Thompson on the same night.
那不算  我喝醉了
That doesn't count: I was drunk.
是达娜在说话吗
Is that Dana?
一旦你厌倦这个誓言之后
As soon as you get bored with this whole pledge thing,
你就会回到之前的状况了
You're just gonna jump right back in the saddle again.
等你到了大学  别告诉我说
And when you get to college, don't even tell me
你没和女同性恋
That you won't be experimenting
尝试过交往
with the standard lesbian hookups,
3P  还有肛交
Having three-ways, trying anal.
-耶  -耶
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我就说嘛
That's what I'm talking...
放松
Just relax.
-别愣着啊  -信念是...
- Do something! - Faith is...
-她是你女儿  -快去
- She’s your daughter. - Go!
信念坚如磐石...
Faith is the rock-solid...
你不相信我是认真的吗
You don't think I'm committed to this?
我父母就等到结婚后才做
My parents waited until marriage.
我爸和你妈一起上的高中
My dad went to high school with your mom.
他说她上过整个橄榄球队
He said she blew the whole football team
搞得不得不去洗胃
And had to have her stomach pumped.
别这么恶心行不
Don't be gross, okay?
另外  你爸只是替补
Plus, your dad was a beta.
那些家伙可是性交好手
Those guys are notorious poon slayers.
他妈的  全是胡扯
Fuck it! This is bullshit!
你知道你想这么做
You know you want this.
我们错过圣餐了吗
Did we miss communion?
东大瀑布高中的开拓者加油
Go for the East Great Falls Blazers
加油  开拓者
Go, Blazers!
令人惊讶的是
Which is surprising,
鉴于这是本季最后一场主场比赛
since this is the last home game of the season.
他们使出了全部的力气
You'd think they'd really pump up the power there.
小心  盯住他  盯住他
Look at him! Watch that guy! Watch that guy!
尽管现在比分接近平局
Even though it's close to a tie,
哦  天哪  对了  你爸刚才说什么
Oh, my gosh, wait. So, what did your dad say?
他说如果再看到内森在我100英尺内出现
He said if he ever sees Nathan within 100 feet of me,
他会用生锈的园艺工具把他阉了
He's gonna castrate him with a rusty garden weasel.
不是吧  那你们结束了还是怎样
Oh, no. So what? Is it over between you guys or what?
不知道
I don't know.
如果你想整他的话
Well, if you ever want to try a mage,
欢迎加入我和理查德
You're welcome to join Richard and me.
-别  -不用了
- No. - No.
别在戴利教练面前说"年轻男孩"
Please don't say "young boy" around Coach Daly.
没错  他是...
Yeah, out here he's...
-那你呢  美女  -什么
- What about you, missy? - What?
你的性生活啊
How's your sex life?
拜托  我打算开始性生活  是的  没错
You guys, I'm gonna go through with it. I am. I am.
真无聊
You're so boring.
我以为你在图书馆脱衣服后
I would've thought you'd be fielding offers
早就已经都搞定了
After your striptease in the library.
是的  我只是在等待好的时机
Yeah, I’m... I'm still just waiting for the right time.
蓝白军  先前冲  加油  必胜
Blue and white, let's go, fight, win.
向前冲  加油  必胜
Let's go, fight, win.
蓝白军  向前冲  加油  必胜  开拓者
Blue and white, let's go, fight, win. Blazers!
加油  必胜  蓝白军  向前冲  加油  必胜
Fight, win. Blue and white, let's go, fight, win.
我想你拍啦啦队拍得够多了吧
I think that is quite enough pictures of the cheerleaders.
应该多拍点比赛吧
How about we get some of the game?
继续
As you were.
蠢货
Douche bag.
蓝白军
Blue and white...
希尔森把球带到了前场
Shearson's bringing the ball up court.
把球传给了斯科特・斯戴福尔
He passes it off to Scott Stifler.
中心高中队拦下了希尔森的球
Central takes a charge from Shearson.
时间到  开拓者  现在该怎么做呢  比尔
Time out, Blazers. What are we gonna do now, bill?
离比赛结束还有10秒
Ten seconds in the game.
我想他们该好好努力打下去
I think these guys really need to get their act
用心比赛  傻子
Get your head in the game, doggy style.
你可以比赛完了再做你的春梦
You can finish your wet dream later.
-对不起  -比赛情况就是这样
- I'm sorry. - This is it for this game.
嗨  斯科特  我能和你说两句吗
Hey, Scott? Can I talk to you for a sec?
你疯了吗  我还在比赛
Are you nuts? I'm in the middle of a game.
本赛季的最后一场主场比赛
Last home game of the season.
真的让他们好好行动起来
Really gotta get their act together.
89平  还剩3.9秒
Tie game, 89 all, 3:9 seconds left.
看看会发生什么
Let's see what's gonna happen here.
-中心队得球  -冲啊  开拓者
- Central’s got the ball. - go, Blazers!
他们现在占优势
They have the advantage.
看起来...  双掩护
Looks like... Double screen!
希尔森得球了  太好了  进了
Shearson gets the ball. It's good! It's in!
比赛结束  91比89  东大瀑布的开拓者获胜
The game's over. 91-89 for East Great Falls Blazers.
不可思议  朋友们
This is incredible, folks!
这意味着我们打入季后赛了
This means we're going on to the playoffs!
不可思议  太激动了
Unbelievable! It's exciting.
今天发生的这些太美妙了
What a chain of events that has occurred here today!
亲爱的  我们得谈谈
Honey, I need to talk to you.
哦  好的
Yeah, sure.
那个...是圣经吗
Is...is that a bible?
什么  不是  这是...
What? No. No, it's...
亲爱的  读圣经没什么不好啊
Well, honey, it's okay to read the bible.
我的意思是  你表现得
I mean, gosh, you act like
像我抓到你读色情书
I caught you reading pornography.
你刚要说什么来着
What did you wanna talk about?
我刚收到我的信用卡账单
Well, I just got my credit card statement and...
你的刷卡记录里
And here on your card
有项来自内衣店
There's a charge here for a lingerie store.
是的...我会把钱还你的  老妈
Yeah, I’m... I'm gonna pay you back for that, mom.
你谈恋爱了吗
Is there a girl you're seeing?
不是  老妈  这很复杂
No. Mom, it's complicated.
-你是买给自己的吗  -不是
- did you buy something for yourself? - no!
你对这方面好奇很正常
Because it's a very normal area of exploration.
书上说
My book says that
某些恋物癖不代表就是同性恋
Most fetishes are not homosexual in nature,
而且  你知道的  男孩子么...
And, well, you know, boys, they tend to...
好了老妈  没错  你说的对
Yes, mom, that's it. You figured it out.
我就是喜欢穿女性的内衣
I love wearing women's underwear.
小内裤  丁字裤  还有连衫衬裤
Thongs, g-strings, a little teddy now and then.
穿起来又软又滑  有花边的更好
It's so soft and silky smooth. The frillier the better.
淫荡啊
Sexy.
天哪  拜托
Oh, god! Come on.
搞定
Gotcha.
所以是给女生的咯
So it was for a girl.
是的  老妈
Yeah, mom.
很好
Great.
你还记得在舞会前你和我说的话吗
So, you know that thing you told me before the dance?
记得
Yeah.
好吧  我在想你说的那些话
Right, well, I was thinking about that conversation.
怎么了
So, what about it?
我在想  我觉得  你或许该等等
I was just thinking, you know, maybe you should wait.
我知道  我也一直在想这事儿
I know. You know, I’ve thought about it, too,
但我一直觉得这整件事
But I still feel like I'm making this whole thing
好像  变成了一个大问题
Into, like, this huge deal.
我的意思是  它一直困扰着我
I mean, it's consuming my every thought.
我不知道该怎么做  罗伯
I don't know, Rob.
我总觉得搞定这件事是最好的
I still feel like it's best if I just get it over with.
没错  我懂
Yeah. I can see that.
你说的对  我就是喜欢穿女性的内衣
You figured it out. I love wearing women's underwear.
小内裤  丁字裤  还有连衫衬裤
Thongs, g-strings, a little teddy now and then.
穿起来又软又滑  有花边的更好
It's so soft and silky smooth. The frillier the better.
这是什么东西  蠢货
What is up with this crap, butt nugget?
这完全是断章取义
That was taken completely out of context.
我当时说的是玩笑话
All right? I was being facetious.
他的意思是他不是当真的
That means he wasn't being serious.
我知道玩笑是什么意思  蠢货
I know what facetious means, dick face.
你是想全校的女生都讨厌你吗
Are you trying to repel all the pussy in school?
-不是  -滴答滴答  和狗搞的人
- No... - Tick tock, doggy boy.
性福时间到
You cock is on the clock.
让一下  记得做好笔记
Excuse me. Take notes.
-嗨  伊莫金  -斯戴福尔
- Hey, Imogen. - Stifler.
今天的关键词是腿
The word for the day is legs
所以呢
So?
为何不去我那
So, why don't we go back to my place
探讨一下这个词
And spread the word?
为什么你不省口气
Well, how about you save your breath?
还是留着对你的马子说吧
You're gonna need it to inflate your date later.
绅士们  是找个妞上床的时候了
Gentlemen, it is time we got laid.
是吗   我们不是一直想这么做吗
Really? And what is it we've been trying to do all this time?
不不  我们得做爱
No, no. We need to get laid.
这写着  1995年9月9号
Right here. September 9th, 1995.
你能不能说个简洁扼要的纲领
Can you give us the executive summary?
不  不是那个  看这
No, not that. This.
我们得来次公路旅行
We are going on a road trip.
你们打算在加拿大呆多长时间
How long do you intend on staying in Canada?
就几个小时
Just a couple of hours.
你们来这干什么
What's the nature of your visit?
我们驱车好几百英里来这找辣妹
We've driven many miles in search of vertical smiles.
这用的是公里
We use kilometres here.
那我们驱车几百公里来这润滑一下老二
Then we've driven many clicks to wet our dicks?
是这样
Yes! Yeah!
-这行得通吧  对吧  -拜拜
- That works, right? - Bye bye.
操你们美国佬
Fucking Americans.
加拿大的外汇率
You know, the exchange rate
真的能帮我们解决不少问题
On the dollar is really gonna help us out.
是的
Yeah.
好的  前面路口右拐
Okay, up ahead, turn right.
-你确定吗  -是的  右拐
- You sure? - Yes. Turn right.
好的  伙计们  我们开始吧
Okay, boys. Let's do this.
你确定这是个好主意
Are you sure this is a good idea?
快点  孬种  我们去找点乐子
Come on, you pussy. Let's get laid.
性经上说我们得找莫妮克
The bible says to ask for Monique.
嗨  你是莫妮克吗
Hi. Are you Monique?
不不不不...
No, moi, no, no, no. mais,
莫妮克  她在里面
Monique, she is inside.
进来  进来  小伙子
Come. Come, boys.
小伙子们  这是我们的房子（法语）
Boys, entrez chez nous.
很漂亮  不是吗
C'est magnifique, no?
我这就去叫莫妮克
I will get Monique.
见到你  她肯定会很高兴
She will be so happy to see you.
在此期间  请自便
In the meantime, make yourselves at home.
天啊  真是波涛汹涌
Jesus, tits.
看来我们是来对地方了
We came to the right place.
那是头麋鹿吗
Is that a moose?
要套套吗
Condom?
为什么  谢谢
Why, thank you.
先生们
Gentlemen.
谢谢
Thank you.
很感谢
Very much.
谢谢
Thank you.
真想快点见到莫妮克
Can't wait to see Monique.
我们是来找莫妮克的
We're here to see Monique.
我就是莫妮克
I am Monique.
那...挺好的
Well, that's...that's okay.
过来  过来  让我给你们倒杯美酒
Come, come. I make you a nice drink.
你能给我们一分钟时间吗
Could you just give us just one minute?
也许能够让我们学到不少知识
This could be very educational for all of us.
是吗
Really?
他准备好了
He's up.
不不  为什么我第一个
No, no. Why am I first?
这是你的主意
It was your idea.
不要...欺负莫妮克
Don't...don't insult Monique.
她可在书里占了整整一章
She has an entire chapter in the bible.
快点  你会很享受的
Come on, you're going to have a nice time.
你们两个疯子玩得开心
You two crazy kids have fun.
热烈欢迎
And welcome.
那...应该怎么做
So...so, how does this work?
我该付你钱吗
Am I supposed to pay you?
不不不  现在不需要
No, no, no. Not yet.
我明白了
I see.
你是在做白日梦呢  年轻人
You've got one active imagination, boy.
我出神多长时间了
How long was I out?
这次只有八秒钟
Only about eight seconds that time.
不  不  不  不  不...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. no. no. no, no, no.
对  对
Yes. yes.
莫妮克  做得太赞了
Monique! That's really nice.
就是这样
That's it.
很抱歉  我一般会挺很久
I'm so sorry. I usually last a lot longer.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  我该拍一下你的肩或是什么吗
Hey, was I supposed to tap you on the shoulder or something?
哦  不要啊
Oh, no. No.
救命  救命  救命  救命
Help! help! help, help, help!
快  快  我来了
Go, go, go! go! I'm coming!
-我的天  伙计  -上帝啊
- Jesus. Dude. - Oh, god!
怎么了  你难道还想要个观众吗
What, do you need an audience?
不  不  等等  伙计
No, no. Wait, guys.
我猜她是死了
I think she's dead!
你说什么
Excuse me?
天啊  这可不妙
Oh, my god. This is not good.
我甩不开她
I can't get her off.
我估计她是突发心脏病了
I think she had a heart attack.
快来帮忙
Help!
我猜她是得了牙关紧闭症
she's got lockjaw.
快帮我把她弄开
Get her off of me!
哦 我的天啊
oh, my god. oh, my god.
是牙关紧闭证
It's lockjaw.
夹住了  夹住了  夹住了  夹住了
Lockjaw! Lockjaw, lockjaw, lockjaw, lockjaw, lockjaw!
-好吧  -快帮我弄开
- Okay. - Get her off!
抱歉
I'm sorry!
电话  电话  稍等  让开
Phone. Phone. Wait. Clear!
该死的  我在干什么
Shit. What am I doing?
让开  再来一次
Clear, clear!
好的  从下面入手
Okay. Come down here.
抓住她的腿  一二三
Grab her legs. One, two, three.
算了吧  完全被卡住了  上帝啊
Forget it. It's totally screwed up.Oh, god.
你们对妈妈干了什么
What you do to maman?
妈妈  你们杀了妈妈
Maman! You killed maman!
你们杀了妈妈
You killed maman!
操你们美国佬  快给我滚回来
Fucking Americans! Come back here.
我要剁了你们  我要剁了你们这群懦夫
I'll kill you! I'll kill you, you cowards!
我杀了她
I killed her.
我的精液把她害死了
I killed her with my sperm!
伙计
Hey, man
阎王要你二更死  不会留你到五更
When it's your time to go, it's your time to go.
她人生已经很完整了
She led a full life.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
伙计  你想要我说什么
Man, what do you want me to say?
说你杀了她吗
You're the one that murdered her!
真不敢相信
I can't believe that was the woman
她就是性经上说的做爱对象
The bible said we should have sex with.
这儿  1995年9月9号
Right here,"September 9th, 1995:"
我来看看
Let me see that.
不  不  那是7!
No. no, that's a seven!
是1975  是70年代
That's 1975. It's from the '70s.
-我以为是九  -闭嘴  闭嘴
- I thought it was a nine. - Shut up! Shut up!
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything!
闭嘴  闭嘴  我想回家
Shut up! Just shut up! I wanna go home.
我不想来这
I don't wanna be here.
上帝啊  我刚刚碾了只松鼠
Oh, my god! I just hit a squirrel.
投得不错
Well, that went well.
伙计们  现在得按照我说的做
Guys, I think it's time we try my interpretation.
听着  内森
Look, Nathan
你想说服达娜和你上床
You've been trying to convince Dana to sleep with you
而不是对她言听计从是吧
Instead of just listening to her. Right, you know?
为何不从她的角度考虑一下
Trying to see things from her point of view?
给她...
Showing just...
...一点点的尊重
Just a little respect.
还有你
And you, you're still
你还在引诱女孩子和你上床
Trying to trick women into sleeping with you
而不是坦诚相待
Instead of just being honest.
你还不是个不敢告诉
And you're still too much of a pussy
海蒂自己喜欢她的孬种
To tell Heidi you're into her.
(图书馆入口)
你今晚会去斯戴福尔那吗
You going to Stifler's house tonight?
是的  我有可能和达娜一块
Yeah. I'll probably go with Dana.
那个你想赶快解决的事有什么进展吗
So any luck losing that thing you were trying to get rid of?
-罗伯  -我只是随便问问
- Rob. - I'm just asking.
也许你该少管闲事
Maybe you should mind your own business.
你今天怎么了
What's with you today?
我想跟你说件
I wanna tell you something that
很早之前就想告诉你的事
I've been wanting to say for a long time.
好的
Okay.
我很喜欢你
I really like you.
我也很喜欢你
I really like you, too.
不  不是那样的  我是真的很喜欢你
No, not like that. I really like you.
-罗伯  -我觉得你很棒
- Rob... - I think you're great.
你性格好  很会说笑话
You have a great personality. I laugh at all your jokes.
还有你很漂亮
You're pretty.
天啊  你很漂亮  闻起来都这么香
Oh, god, you're pretty. You even smell great.
我不知道  只是...
I don't know. I'm just...
和你在一起很快乐
I'm happy when I'm around you.
我不知道你是否有这样的感觉
Now, I don't know if you feel the same way
如果有的话...
but if you do...
那我们就不要再浪费时间了
Let's not waste any more time.
好吗  我们...
Right? let's just
试着跟着感觉走
See where our feelings take us.
我也有同样的感觉
I feel the same way.
-真的吗  -是的
- You do? - Yes.
这太棒了  你为什么不说呢
This is great. Why didn't you say something?
你为什么不说
Why didn't you?
时间到了  我得走了  晚上见
It's about that time, so I gotta go. but I'll see you tonight?
好的
Yes.
爸爸
Dad?
她过来了
There she is.
他们看到我了  快蹲下  蹲下
They saw me! Get down! Get down!
哦  上帝啊  上帝啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my gosh.
快开车
Drive. drive.
没什么  没什么
It's cool. It's cool.
内森  听着  我在想
Nathan, look, I've been thinking.
或许我对你太苛刻了
Maybe I've been too hard on you.
有吗
You have?
看得出你喜欢我女儿
You obviously love my daughter,
你们应该在一起
And you two should be together.
-我们应该吗  -当然
- We should? - Absolutely.
亲爱的  这样招待人家可不对
Honey, it is not right to give a man blue balls.
如果你想男孩子喜欢自己
If you want boys to like you
就得秀出来
you gotta put out.
先从内森的朋友入手
Here, start with nathan's friend.
这真是逊毙了
This is so not cool.
意淫你死党的女朋友吗
I mean, fantasising about your best friend's girlfriend?
哦  上帝啊
Oh, my god!
-爸爸  不要  -操你他妈的混蛋
- Dad! Stop! Stop. - Fucknut!
好的  女孩们
All right, girls.
-派对看起来不错  -是的
- Party looks good. - Yeah.
听我说  集中精神
All right, listen to me. Stay focused.
坦白点  尊重对方
Be honest, show respect
说出自己心声
And just say whatever's on your mind.
闭嘴  混球
Stop, jerk.
甚至都不能接近达娜
I can't even get near Dana.
她很快就到  和海蒂一起
She'll be here. She's coming with Heidi.
尽量设身处地为她着想
Just try and think of things from her point of view.
这点如果我在行的话
Yeah, and I might as well just crack the da vinci code
达芬奇密码早被我解出来了
While I'm at it.
给她送点乳香精油和没药
Just get her some frankincense and myrrh.
好主意
That's a great idea.
如果不奏效的话我会给你好果子吃
I'll just pick up some roofies for you while I'm out.
据我所知  那得有配方才行
You need a prescription for that, from what I hear.
卢贝  听仔细  这对你也有用
Lube, pay attention. This applies to you, too.
我们进去后  尽量保持自我
All right. Let's try to go in there and just be real.
好的  奥普拉
All right, Oprah.
嘿  那不是从中心高中来的妞吗
Hey. Isn't that that chick from Central?
没错
Yeah.
嘿  斯戴福尔
Hey, Stifler.
嘿  你叫
Oh, hey, there...
是凯蒂
Katie.
对  是凯蒂  我当然知道
Katie, right. I knew that.
只是和你开个玩笑
Just having some fun with you.
我能和你谈谈吗  就我俩的谈话
Can I talk to you for a second, like, in private?
可以  你知道吗
Yeah, sure, you know what?
我再去拿杯酒  随后就来找你
Let me just grab another beer and I'll be right back with you.
不要放我鸽子
Don't you flake on me.
-伙计看来收获不错  -我不这么认为
- Dude, you been working out? - Didn't think so.
-你们两个真能扛  -上帝
- You two, stay amazing. - My god.
嘿  怎么样  美人儿
Hey, what's up, beautiful?
我上周末烂醉如泥
You know, I got so drunk last weekend
结果把自己的小弟弟钉在桌上
That I nailed my cock to a table
放在火上烤
then set it on fire.
想检查一下吗
Wanna check it out?
检查桌子还是你的老二
The table or your cock?
天啊  我爱死那个腔调了
God, I love that accent.
你能够帮我个忙  说一下...
Could you do me a favour and just say,
"打我的屁股  斯戴福尔"
"spank me, Stifler. "
"打我的小屁股"
"Spank me wee little bum."
你怎么知道我喜欢被人打屁股
How did you know I like to be spanked?
太棒了
Awesome!
那个你一直叨叨念念的
So where's this boyfriend Richard you
男友理查德哪去了
Keep talking about non-stop all the time?
他不参加高中派对
He doesn't attend high-school parties.
听起来你是想要些
Sounds like you might be
国产的美国牛肉啊
In the market for some home-grown American beef.
对不起  我是素食主义者
Sorry, I'm vegan.
干杯
Cheers.
那用黄瓜行吗
What if I use a cucumber?
伙计们  就在今晚
All right, boys. Tonight's the night.
快祝我好运
Wish me luck.
祝你好运  伙计
Good luck, buddy.
Good luck, dude.
今晚  你将成为真正的男人
Tonight, you become a man.
说得对  今晚  我要做爱
That's it. Tonight, I'm getting laid!
-是的  伙计  -是的  伙计
- Yeah, buddy! Yes! - Yeah, buddy.
-是的  -就在这
- Yes! - Right here.
开始的时候慢点温柔点
Just give it to her nice and slow at first.
然后加快节奏
Then speed her up.
达娜
Dana!
我找遍了  没见到海蒂
I can't find Heidi anywhere.
或许她根本就没来
Maybe she didn't come.
不  不 她的车就停在外面
No, no. Her car is outside.
你认为是怎么回事
How you making out?
看那边
Check it out.
你难道不觉得或许
Don't you think maybe
艾什莉对你来说太有难度吗
Ashley's just a little bit out of your league?
我不知道  我只是想说
I don't know. I'm just saying, you know
你已经盯上她好几年了
You've been at it for years.
或许你和她之间没有可能
Maybe it's just not in the cards for you.
我是个有修养的人
I'm a man of refinement.
能得十分为什么要去得六分呢
Why settle for a six when you can get a perfect 10?
好吧  随便你怎么说  祝你好运了
Okay, whatever you say, man. Good luck.
我要行动了
Right. I'm gonna do it.
嘿  你怎样  艾什莉
Hey, what's up, ashley?
嘿  卢贝
Hey, Lube.
要啤酒吗
You want a beer?
有了
Got a beer.
对
Right.
那么
So...
你肯定知道我非常喜欢你  对吧
You obviously know that I'm, like, totally into you. Right?
是啊  我去求过签的
Yeah. I've seen the Shrine.
好的
All right.
那我就跟你坦诚布公
Okay, so I'm just gonna be honest with you.
实话实说
I'm just gonna lay it out on the line.
并且毫无保留的
No tricks, no hidden agenda at all.
我碰巧是个敏感专业的情人
I happen to be a sensitive and expert lover.
我保证让你爽到极限
I can guarantee that I will satisfy you in every way possible,
在你飘飘欲仙之前
And I shall not stop until I'm certain
我绝不会停止
That you are completely happy with my endeavours.
好的
Okay.
听着  说得真吸引人啊
Look, that was a really interesting speech,
我也不想在
And I don't really wanna embarrass you in front of
众人面前让你出丑
everyone, but...
但我们之间是不可能的
But it's not gonna happen.
我是说  我知道你超酷
I mean, I think that you're, like, really super cool,
班里班外看起来也都很可爱
And you're really funny in class and everything,
但我不想跟你做爱
But I don't wanna have sex with you.
明白吗
Okay?
当然  当然  好的
Yeah, yeah. Sure. Okay.
-没事吧  -当然  当然
- So are we cool? - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
好的
All right.
我要再去拿杯啤酒  你还要吗
Well, I'm gonna go get another beer. Do you want one?
不  不  不用了  谢谢
No, no. I'm...I'm good. I'm good.
你刚才说什么
What you said just now?
怎么了
Yeah?
是真的吗
Was that true?
保证满意而且绝不
Guaranteed satisfaction and you won't
停止除非女生爽歪之后
Stop until a girl is completely satisfied?
当然
Yeah.
那好吧  管它呢
All right. Well, what the hell.
到楼上左边第一间卧室找我
Meet me upstairs in the first bedroom to the left.
我要和艾米做爱了
事实上  我一直都对你施压
The truth is, yes, I was trying to pressure you,
因为我太想  太想做爱了
Because I really, really wanna have sex.
但我只想跟你做爱
But I really wanna have sex with you.
而且一直以来
And, also, I mean, with us,
约会也总以我为中心
hooking up has always been about me.
我想改变一下
I wanna forget myself for once
来好好满足一下你
And try to make you feel good for a change.
就像  让你满足我那样
Like, maybe try and make you feel the way that
满足你
You make me feel.
别看  别看  那是我的手机
You shouldn't...You shouldn't... It's my phone.
别看我的手机
Don't read my phone.
这是什么意思  "给她一剂炭疽病毒"
What's this supposed to mean? "Give her a dose of manthrax"?
我不知道  我也不知道什么意思
Well, I don't...what does that...
我也不知道  你知道吗
I don't know what that... Do you know what that means?
"我要上床了"
"I'm getting laid"?
还没发生你就到处宣扬
You're advertising this before it even happens?
-不  -哇
- No. - Wow.
你还真是个怪异的变态
You must be some special kind of asshole.
不  不  不  不  我没有  那是
No. no, no, no! no. I didn't...It was...
等着吧  你个败寇
Later, loser.
再快点  好的  现在  慢点 就这样
Faster. Okay. Now, slower. Yes, Yes.
再慢点  舔外阴  对  就这样
Slower. Tickle the bunny. Yes, Yes.
天呢  开始高潮了
Oh, God, the man in the boat is out.
继续  继续  口交舌功  打卷
Paddle, paddle, do the Alphabet. Swirl.
回到外阴那  太爽了  往左边移
Back to the bunny. That's it. Okay. Now, more to the left.
再往左点
More to the left!
-我左边还是你左边  -我左边
- My left or your left? - My left, my left, my left!
好的
All right.
嗨  看见海蒂了吗
Hey, have you seen Heidi?
谢谢
Thanks.
嗨  罗伯
Hey, Rob.
海蒂
Heidi?
狗仔  告诉过你  打个盹你就输了
Hey, doggy style. I told you, you snooze, you lose.
若不想看我们做爱  就走人  变态
So unless you want mop-up duty, close the door, pervert.
你去哪
Hey, where are you going?
这个主意太差劲了
This was a horrible idea.
罗伯  借过一下
Rob? Excuse me.
借过一下  罗伯  罗伯
Excuse me. Rob. Rob.
-走开  -我不想
- Go away. - I didn't. I...
我现在不想看见你
I don't wanna see your face right now.
罗伯
Rob.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你不是说不管自己
What happened to forgetting about yourself
就让我爽吗
And making me feel good?
但是我想
But I thought I just...
什么  你想什么  内森
What? You thought that what, Nathan?
你就假装关心我的想法
That you could just pretend that you cared about
在意我的誓言
My feelings and my pledge
然后再趁机占我便宜吗
And then just go and try again when my guard was down?
不  你没明白  我
No. You don't get it. I...
不  不  是你没搞明白
No. no, you're the one that's not gonna get it.
兄弟  你要悠着点
Dude, you need to slow down.
是啊  真的  我们还是回去吧
Yeah, seriously. Let's just go home.
对  对  关于《索爱天书》  你说的对
You, Sir... you, Sir, were right about the Bible.
因为贱人喜欢做爱
Because assholes get laid!
对
Yes.
不  不  不  兄弟  你才是对的
No. no, no, dude. You were right.
-里面蕴意深刻  -你在说什么
- There's something to it. - What are you talking about?
我们试着做好男
We tried the nice guy thing
还保留着处男身
and I believe we're all still virgins.
而这种好男情怀让我越界了
Well, the nice guy vibe got me past the bouncer, man.
绅士们  你们都输了
Well, gentlemen, you failed,
因为你们都嫉妒
And the proof, as they say, is in the jell-o.
兄弟们  一会见
So I will see you later, nice guys.
我知道你对我感兴趣
I know you want me.
我跟你上楼  让你爽死
I'm gonna let you take me upstairs and do me right now.
-真的  -当然
- Really? - Yeah.
吻我
Kiss me.
嗨  女士们
Hey, ladies.
哦  天啊
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
瞧瞧这帮骚女
Look at those taters!
从后面干我
Do me from behind.
什么
What?
我以为你喜欢后进式
I thought you liked it doggy style.
你在那干什么呢  进来啊
What are you doing back there? let's go.
你不会把你的弟弟插进去是吧
You're not putting your dick in that, are you?
你搞啥  太恶心了
Are you kidding me? Gross.
给你  喝点这个有好处
Here. This'll help.
谢谢
Thanks.
亲爱的  我知道
Honey, I know that
我不能阻止你做某些事
I can't stop you from doing certain things,
但你一定要注意安全
But I can insist that you are safe.
你有没有酒后驾车
Did you drink and drive?
没有  约翰・卡斯特罗开车送我回来的
No. John Costello drove me home.
我只是想告诉你
I want you to know that
即便欲火焚身
if you find yourself in any carnal situation,
也要注意安全措施
That you...You will use protection.
你说欲火指什么啊
What do you mean by carnal?
这个
This.
你搞啥  太恶心了
Are you kidding me? gross.
现在还有隐私没有
Is there no such thing as privacy any more?
我会告诉你父亲
I will tell your father that
说你今天不能见他
You're just not up to seeing him today.
你不太舒服
You're not feeling well.
谢谢
Thanks.
她怎么样
How was she?
-谁  -你吐的那个女孩
- How was who? - Vomit girl.
你怎么知道
How do you know about that?
那你认为是谁把这些视频给妈妈看
Who do you think is forwarding all those videos to mom?
我要放弃了
I'm ready to give up.
我认为我知道问题答案了
I thought I had the answers.
《索爱天书》99%都不能读
It's too bad that 99% of the Bible's completely unreadable.
这样好了
That's it.
我们来重编《索爱天书》
We need to reconstruct the Bible.
为什么
Why?
因为秘密都在这
The secrets are in there.
想要上床不是一下两下能搞定的
I mean, there's no one single answer to getting laid.
对吧  我们需要通读才行
Right? We need the whole book to understand.
说不定还有好多我们需要知道的呢
Probably has a lot of crap in there that we need to know, too,
比如位置  技巧  插入角度
Like positions, techniques, angle of insertion.
没错  《索爱天书》就是
Exactly. That's what the Bible was created for,
给我们这种人看的
To help guys like us.
我们亏欠别人  是我毁了这本书
And we owe it to the others. I ruined the bible.
为了未来的人  我也要恢复这本书的精华
I owe it to future generations to restore its wisdom.
哥们  我也想这么做  但怎么做
Dude, I'm all for it, but how?
从谁开始
Where do we start?
从最早开始
From the beginning.
肯定是这个人创了《索爱天书》
This must be the guy who created the Bible.
诺亚・莱文斯坦
哪位
Hello?
您好  请问诺亚・莱文斯坦在吗
Hi, may I speak to Noah Levenstein, please?
请讲
Speaking.
是你创了《圣经》吗
Are you the one who created the Bible?
不  应该是上帝
No, that would be God.
等等
Hold on.
我指的是《索爱天书》
I'm referring to the Bible.
我是从东大瀑布高中打来的
I'm calling from east great falls high school.
那是1969年高三夏天
It was the summer of my junior year, 1969,
我跟朋友一块去阿姆斯特丹玩
And my buddies and I, we take this trip to Amsterdam,
碰上一群还不错的荷兰淫女
Where we run into a group of semi-attractive Dutch nymphos
愿意卖身换一把
Who were willing to trade their bodies for
吉米・亨德里克斯LPS系列电吉他
a handful of Jimi Hendrix LPS.
毋庸置疑
Well, needless to say,
那个周末我们和那群小妞玩的超爽
we had ourselves one super weekend with those gals,
我指性趣上  如果你理解我说的
Sexually speaking, if you get my drift.
但不幸的是  我们都懵懂无知
But the sad news was, we had no idea what we were doing.
什么技巧也不会
We had no technique.
但有一天  我们外出观光时
And then one day, we were out sight-seeing,
我们在红灯区碰上一个荷兰妓女
And we run into this dutch hooker in the red-light district,
她跟我们提起有这么一本书
And she tells us about this book.
一本性爱指南
It was a sex manual,
是由19世纪某个牧师写的
evidently written in the 19th century by some priest.
我们详读了一遍又一遍
Well, we read that thing cover to cover,
然后回到东大瀑布高中
And then when we got back to east great falls,
我有了写一本自己的书的想法
I had the bright idea to write my own book
写上自己的观察  经验和建议
And add my own observations and experiences and advice
然后把它留在图书馆
And leave it in the library for some
给那些不幸处男后辈们
Other hapless virgin in the class below us.
但我没想到居然流传了40年
But I had no idea it had been passed down for 40 years.
您的书简直是个传奇  莱文斯坦先生
Your book is a legend, Mr. Levenstein.
你们带了吗
Do you have it here?
带了
Yeah.
我能看一下吗
May I see it?
哦  天啊
Oh, my.
孩子们
Boys.
这可真有点历史了
This is a real piece of history here.
它怎么了
What happened to it?
这就是我们来的原因了
Well, that's why we're here.
《索爱天书》有点被毁了
The Bible kinda got ruined,
所以我们想咨询相关作者来进行重编
So we wanna call everyone on the list and try to reconstruct it.
那看来你们是需要帮助了
Well, I think you boys might need some help.
女孩们通常有优势
Well, girls have the advantage,
因为她们会彼此聊天
because girls talk to each other,
不是跟你们开玩笑  她们连阴茎都聊
And don't kid yourself, they talk about the penis.
阴茎大小  形状  弯曲角度
Penis size, penis shape, the angle of the bend.
不管你注意没注意的  她们都聊
Whether it winks at you. they talk.
真要想跟女人做爱
Now, to really make love to a woman,
首先要真正关心她
You gotta really care about her.
做爱很爽
But...hey, sex is great,
但跟你爱的人做爱才最爽
But sex with someone you love? That's awesome.
哥们  这太有意义了
Dude, that is so profound.
我说嘛
Telling you.
是啊  在路上难免会感觉孤单
Yeah, definitely gets lonely on the road.
当然  我用个各种食物自慰
Sure, I made love to all kinds of different food groups.
你试过用花生酱三明治做爱吗
Did you ever try making love to a peanut-butter sandwich?
超爽
Nothing comes close.
什么
What?
也可用去骨蹄膀
Well, maybe a deboned ham hock,
不过准备起来太麻烦
But that takes a whole lot of prep.
屈膝
Bend your knees.
下次做时  试试印度式
Next time you spank it, sit Indian-Style.
即使是一百万年都不会泄
You won't come, not in a million years.
我们的性器官就像音乐器材
Our sex organs are like musical instruments.
你可以请任何技术员来帮你吹喇叭
Sure, you can have any technician blow on your horn,
但把乐器放入一位真正的专家手中呢
But to place your instrument into the hands of a true expert?
年轻的朋友们  那才是真正的和声
That, my young friend, is true harmony.
男孩们从不交流这方面的事情
Guys don't talk to each other
因为他们视彼此如对手
Because they view each other as competitors,
尽管我觉的这很荒谬
Which I think is crazy. You know?
男人们也需要同心协力
Because men need to help each other and work together
如果想把到妹
To get laid.
诺亚・莱文斯坦  70级
Noah Levenstein, class of '70.
- 皮特・萨姆布雷利  -没错  诺亚・莱文斯坦
- Pete Sambrelli? - That's right, the Noah Levenstein.
你有他的电话吗
Do you have a number for him?
这是一些关于他对润滑剂的使用建议
This is regarding his advice on the lubricants.
我们在女王篇发现了舌转风暴功
We found the tongue tornado in Regina.
还说为朋友两肋插刀
You said bros befo' hos.
是不是你说的  为朋友两肋插刀
Isn't that what you said? bros befo' hos.
那你还上了我女朋友
And then you screwed my girlfriend.
卡里托  合唱团的人都是这样啊
Well, so did the entire glee club, Carlito.
你什么意思
What's your point?
都是生理需求  但信心是关键
It's all about chemistry, and confidence is the key.
相敬如宾  你听过那歌  对不对
R-e-s-p-e-c-t, you've heard that song, right?
孩子们  我们又确认一个
Boys, we got another confirmation.
你要正确的对待你的小姐客户
You gotta treat your lady right.
你需要温柔和蔼
You've got to be gentle, kind
并且尊重你爱的那个人
And respectful to the one you love.
-你在跟谁打电话  -闭嘴
- Who are you talking to? - Shut the fuck up.
这样你才能让她芳心欲动
This is how you get her really excited.
把你的手指插入她的屁眼  相信我
Stick your finger in her ass. Trust me.
用两根还是一根手指
Was that two fingers or one?
对不起  那是机密
I'm sorry. Confidential matter.
电话  电话  好的
Phone, phone. Okay.
然后呢
Then what happened?
你好  对  77级的
Hello. Yeah. Class of '77.
等一下  我找只笔记下
Yeah, hold on. Let me get a pen.
请皮特・奥唐奈听电话
Pete O'donnell, please.
你是谁
Who is this?
奥唐奈先生  我是马歇尔・卢布斯基
Mr O'donnell, this is Marshall Lubetski.
我想和你交流一下《索爱天书》的内容
I just wanted to talk to you about what you wrote in the Bible.
你知道的  是关于你和约翰逊女士的肛交
You know, about having anal sex with Miss Johnson.
非常感谢  划掉马克 S.
Thank you very much! Mark S.!
这不是一本关于性的手册
This is not a sex manual.
这是人生手册
It is a life manual.
我结婚已经35年了
Now, I've been married for 35 years
没有离婚不仅是因为我帅
And not just because I'm this handsome dude
知道怎样满足女人
Who knows how to satisfy a woman.
35年不离不弃是因为我爱我的妻子
I've been married 35 years because I love my wife
我尊重她
And I respect my wife.
无论是在阿姆斯特丹还是东大瀑布高中
And whether it's Amsterdam or East Great Falls
都因为我爱着她
It all comes down to this.
如果你真诚并尊重女孩
If you're honest and treat a girl with respect,
该发生的就会发生
Then whatever happens is meant to happen,
因为这一切都是自然而然的
Because it's all perfectly natural.
孩子们  兵马未动粮草先行
Boys, I've prepared you for this quest.
在你面前的是人生最大的考验
And before you lies the biggest test of your lives.
这本书是强大的杀手?
This book is a powerful weapon,
好好地利用它吧
So use it for good
别适得其反
Not evil.
太好了
Yes.
你还在找吸尘器吗
You still looking for the vacuum?
没  很奇怪它在科迪的房间里
No. I found it in Cody's room. So strange.
我是说我都忘了放在那里了
I mean, I just don't remember leaving it there.
显然我糊涂了
Losing my mind, clearly.
妈妈  我可以参加滑雪旅行吗
Hey, mom, can I go on the ski trip?
好
Yes.
但是别喝酒  如果喝了别开车
But no drinking, and if you do drink, no driving.
别担心 如果我做糗事
Don't worry. If I do anything wrong
Youtube上肯定马上就有了
I'm sure it'll end up on youtube, so.
到了给你打电话
Call you when I get there.
喝酒的环节到了
Drinking round!
-我也要参加  -你在这里干嘛啊
- Deal me in. - What are you doing here?
我叫凯蒂
Katie.
我知道  但你在这里做什么呢
I know. But what are you doing here?
-我也想参加  -好
- I wanna play. - Right.
斯戴福尔  让她参加吧
Just deal her in, Stifler.
有什么关系呢
What's the big deal?
让她参加吧
Yeah, deal her in.
内森
Hi, Nathan.
谢谢你的花
Thanks for the flowers.
我为我以前的行为道歉
I'm sorry about being a jerk.
而且我已经自尝苦果
And, for the record, I've learned my lesson.
我会尊敬你并支持你的的誓言
I'm ready to respect you and support you on your pledge.
真的吗  为什么呢
Really? But why?
我是因为你  而不是性这么做的
I'm in this for you. I'm not in it just to have sex.
我意识到我是因为你才这么做
Well, I realised that I'm in this for you
如果誓言祈祷了某种作用
And if the pledge gets in the way of that
那这个作用会有多好的效果呢
then how good can it really be?
我们两个好像结成了统一战线
Sounds like a good basis for the two
我们好好玩静观其变
Of us to just relax and see what happens.
看我带来一本书
Look. I bought a book.
我正想我们两个
I was thinking that we could
可以从第一页开始然后
Start on page one and then
看周末我们能读到哪里
see how far we get this weekend.
前三章是前奏
The first three chapters are foreplay.
你知道吗  我也正在看一本书
You know, I've actually been reading a book, as well.
你听过舌转风暴吗
Have you ever heard of the Tongue Tornado?
我们走
Okay, let's go.
这肯定很好玩
This is supposed to be fun.
一点都不好玩
This isn't fun.
等一下  你现在智力无边
Just you wait. You possess wisdom now.
相信这本书吧
Trust in the book.
我想问那到底什么意思呢
I mean, what does that mean, anyway?
你觉得我会不会太粘人了
Do you think I'm too clingy?
当然不是
No. no, of course not.
你知道怎么打扑克吗
Do you even know how to play poker?
我知道这个游戏
I know the game.
如果我输了  我就脱光衣服
And I tell you what, if I lose, I'll take off all my clothes.
哟  棒极了
Snap. Nice.
那我输了呢
And if I lose?
向我道歉
You apologise to me.
-为什么呢  甩了你  -对
- For what? Blowing you off?  - Yes.
道歉还不够  那是我的第一次
If it's not enough, it was my first time.
你应该给我更多
I deserve better.
如果我赢了  你不仅要道歉
But if I win, not only do you apologise to me
你得全裸在雪地里跑
You gotta run through the snow naked.
-太棒了  -一言为定
- Yeah. - It's a deal.
亲爱的  开始脱衣服吧
Start stripping, sweetheart.
还没有结束呢
It's not over yet.
运气好吗
Feeling lucky?
你最好期待会有一个5
You better hope for a five on the river, baby.
她真拿到了5  太不可思议了
She got the five! Unbelievable.
天啊
Oh, my god.
-脱掉  -等一下
- Strip. - Hold on a second.
-脱掉  -脱掉
- Strip. - Strip.
脱掉  脱掉  脱掉  脱掉
strip! strip! strip! strip!
Strip! strip! strip! strip!
你们想让我全裸  你们想看吧
You want me to strip? You want some of this?
宝贝们  我真脱了
It's time to get it going, baby!
好啊  我们走
All right, let's go! here we go, baby.
等一下  我们再谈谈吧
Wait, let's talk this over.
该死的  外面冷死了
Shit. it's freezing out here.
现在道歉
Now apologise.
-对不起  -为什么呢
- I'm sorry. - For what?
因为之后我没有给你打电话
I'm sorry for not calling you afterwards.
还有呢
And what else?
我猪狗不如  好了吧
I'm sorry for being a dick, okay?
现在  打开这该死的门
Now, open the stinking door.
开门
Open the door!
告诉所有人你进来后会如何哭
Now, tell everyone how you cry like a little girl after you come.
像娘们儿一样哭好吧
I cry like a girl after I come, okay?
那可是我的极限了
It's a very intense experience for me.
报警
Call 911 .
待会去屋里找你
Hey, I'll meet you at the lodge later.
好啊
Yeah, yeah, sure. go.
海蒂  等一下
Heidi. Wait up.
你介意我和你一起坐吗
Do you mind if I ride up with you?
不介意
Okay.
还好吗
Hey. What's up?
我们一起坐缆车
We...we're in the same gondola.
对啊
Yeah, look at that.
天啊
Oh, god.
我并没有和斯戴福尔上床
I didn't sleep with Stifler.
嗯  我听说
Yeah. I heard.
-你还在讨厌我吗  -没有啊
- But you still hate me? - No.
你为什么这样说呢
No. Why would you say that?
那晚后你都没和我讲过一句话
You haven't said a word to me since that night.
我知道  对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
我觉得我需要时间整理一下思绪
I guess I just... I needed time to work through my feelings.
然后呢  决定什么了吗
And? What did you decide?
吉布斯说斯戴福尔不得不
Gibbs says that Stifler has to sit
在泡沫橡胶甜甜圈垫子上坐六周
On a foam rubber doughnut for six weeks.
他说斯戴福尔
And he says they're talking about
因为冻伤要截肢
Amputating his feet from frostbite.
吉布斯是骗子  斯戴福尔不用截肢的
Gibbs is a liar. Stifler doesn't need amputation.
那可太坏了  我在商店里做爱都得过A
That's too bad. I got an A in shop.
天啊  那是喷鼻声吗
Oh, my. Was that a snort?
心满意足了吧
Come to gloat?
只是在找同性恋罢了
No. Just looking for a fag.
我和一只麋鹿做了并不代表我是同性恋
Just 'cause I took a moose pickle up my ass doesn't mean I'm gay.
很搞笑  屁股怎么样了
Very funny. How's your bum?
好像生了一堆蛋黄酱  不过谢谢关心
Feels like I gave birth to a mayonnaise jar, but thanks for asking.
我听说了你的男朋友  真要命
Hey, I heard about your boyfriend. that really sucks.
我还以为只有高中男生是混蛋呢
Yeah. I thought only high school boys were jerks.
事实并非如此
It turns out they never outgrow it.
伊莫金 希望你不介意
Lmogen, no offence, and
你是我见过最成熟的女孩
you're the most mature girl I know,
但是24岁的男人不适合你
But a 24-year-old dude isn't gonna take a high-school girl seriously.
我想不是吧
I suppose not.
要坐下吗
You wanna sit down?
为什么
What for?
我认为我们可以共同用一个朋友
I just thought we could both use a friend right now.
斯戴福尔
Stifler.
我错了  本能反应
My bad. reflex.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你得自己做决定
You have to make your own decisions.
我还以为我们关系非同寻常
You know, I just... I thought we had something.
我们以前是啊
We did.
现在也是
We do.
我很害怕
I was scared.
为什么呢
Of what?
我真的喜欢你
I really like you.
我只是想初夜非同一般
And I want it to be special.
我只想做做准备工作
I guess I just wanted to be ready.
你和斯戴福尔上床只是为我做准备工作
So you almost had sex with stifler so you'd be ready for me.
对
Yeah.
这是我听过最蠢的话
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
我听说你有过些经验
Well, I heard you got some practise.
其实事实上是什么也没有
You know, the truth is, is nothing happened.
我不想那么随意
I didn't want it to be random like that.
而且
And...
我不想我的第一次给除了你之外的人
I couldn't picture my first time being with anybody else but you.
怎么了
What was that?
不知道
I don't know.
-好像我们被困住了  -对
- Looks like we're stuck. - Yeah.
我们可能会在这里待上一段时间
You know, we could be up here for a while.
对
Yeah.
我能问你一些问题吗
Hey, can I ask you a question?
对  随意问
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
你为什么和像斯戴福尔那样的人渣搞在一起
Why do you hook up with assholes like scott stifler anyway?
你说什么啊  你都不了解我
Excuse me, but you don't know me.
你和其它人都是一样的
You know, you're just the same as all the rest.
我只是一种战利品
I'm just some sort of trophy to you.
你并不关心我  只关心和我睡觉的事
You don't care about me. You just wanna sleep with me,
你认为这是值得炫耀的事
Because you think it's some sort of status symbol.
不好意思
Sorry.
天啊
God.
我们会在这里待多久呢
How long are we gonna be up here?
我来求助
I'll get help.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
这儿并不高  而且有20英尺左右的雪
It's not that far down, and there's, like, 20 feet of snow.
这是你想在我面前表现的吗
What, is this supposed to impress me?
曾经想过
The thought had crossed my mind.
别这样做  第一  这是错误的
Absolutely not. first of all, it's just wrong.
第二  你都不能碰到那扇门
Second of all, you're not even supposed to touch the door.
第三  这十分危险
And third, it's just really dangerous, okay?
别这样  过来
So just get away from there.
对啊  我在想什么呢
Right. What was I thinking?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我的腿好像受伤了
I think I hurt my leg.
笨蛋
Idiot.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
没事吧
Are you okay?
没事  没事
Yeah, I'm fine. no, I'm fine. I'm fine.
你刚刚说我不关心你
About what you said about how I don't care about you
你只是一个战利品  那都不是真的
And you're just a trophy, that's actually not true.
我真的喜欢你  我们一起上的小学
I really like you. We went to elementary school together.
我还记得你在六年级表演唱的《嘿  你好》
I remember when you sang Hey Ya! in the sixth-grade talent show.
我还记得你在回家游戏中从金字塔上摔下
I remember when you fell off the pyramid at the homecoming game
大一的时候
Freshman year.
你当时很  不过我不介意
You were so embarrassed, but I didn't care.
摔下就好像是你表演的一部分
I just liked how you played it off like it was all part of the routine.
是啊  你是学校的风云人物
I mean, yeah, sure, you're a super-hot babe,
我只是喜欢你这个人
But I actually like you for you.
可能你会觉得很突兀
Look, this may be a shock to you,
但我不知道怎么和女孩交流
But I have no idea what I'm doing with girls.
我真的想好好学学
But I really wanna learn.
你给了我机会
You just give me a chance.
这是我所有的愿望
That's all I'm asking.
我保证我会为你的幸福
And I guarantee that I will make it my life's mission
奋斗终生
To satisfy you in every way possible.
-走  我们回去  -回到缆车上
- Let's go back to the... - to the cabin.
伙计  你忘了签字了
Dude. You forgot to sign it.
你确定我们不能再留它一年吗
You sure we can't just keep it for one more year?
不能  轮到其他人了
No, guys, it's someone else's turn.
这是我的弟弟科迪
Rob on computer. This is my little brother, Cody,
他每天都用吸尘器这样做
And this is what he does with the vacuum every day.
天啊
No! hey! no!
救命啊  塞住了  我不能把它取下来
Help! it's stuck! I can't get it off!
救命啊  塞住了
Help! Help! it's stuck.
逮住你了
Gotcha.
救命
Help!
不
No!
她过去利用我  真糟糕
She was using me. l...that was really bad.
神父  你为什么抛弃了我
Father, why hast thou forsaken me?
想更淫荡地对我口淫吗
Wanna suck me off in the sharper lmage?
罗伯  你是不是特会甜言蜜语啊
Rob, are you some kind of jive turkey?
他都不像他本人了
He's like an inch away from the real McCoy.
带避孕套了吗
Did you bring condoms?
什么
What?
我从13岁开始就想做爱了
I wet the bed until I was 13 years old, okay?
你们没有机会去乔纳斯兄弟的演唱会
You nancy boys couldn't get lucky at a Jonas Brothers concert
纵使有很多后台通行证
With a fistful of backstage passes.
相信上帝和他对生命永恒的承诺
Faith in god and his promise of eternal life.
现在  把避孕套套上香蕉
Now, put the condom on the banana.
谁没有看到啊  看看时间  得走了
Who didn't see that coming? Look at the time. gotta go.
我觉得关于拉拉队的照片太多了
I think that is quite enough pictures of the cheerleaders.
照点比赛的
How about we get some of the game?
正吃着呢
We're eating.
你们是该死的美国人吗
You've been fucking americans or...
看着  爱着
Watching, loving...
容忍我一下
Bear with me.
如果她沮丧  送她花
If she's down, bring her flowers.
她渴了  给她来一杯香槟
If she's thirsty, serve her fine champagne.
我告诉你  我妻子太他妈性感了
Yeah, 'cause, I'm telling you, my wife is pretty effing hot.
我说的是十分紧十分干净的阴口
I'm talking a tight, tight ass and squeaky clean.
很多奶油吗  太好了
Is that cream-filled? You rock.
拜托你别提了
Oh. Don't mention that, okay?
做爱的时候
And whenever it comes to making out,
摆出齐柏林飞船四世(乐队)的架子
Put on side one of Led Zeppelin IV.
--=糖涂口 制作=--